Guide to the David Trinidad Papers ca. 1970-2002 MSS.106
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series I: Correspondence
  - Subseries A: General Correspondence 1970-1998
    - STANFORD, ANN. 4 letters, 1 postcard; dated 1977-1981; plus handwritten copy of "The Informer"; copy of AS's last manuscript, Dreaming the Garden; and miscellaneous poems and announcements. (Box 5, Folder 300)
    - STANFORD, ANN. copy of AS's last manuscript, Dreaming the Garden, undated (Box 5, Folder 301)
    - STEIN, JEAN. 1 letter; dated 1989. (Box 5, Folder 302)
    - STEINKE, DARCEY. 1 letter; dated 1997. (Box 5, Folder 303)
    - STRINGER, ALAN. 2 letters; dated 1984-1985. (Box 5, Folder 304)
    - SWEITZER, JUSTIN. 1 letter; dated 1993. (Box 5, Folder 305)
    - TALCOTT, WILLIAM. 1 letter; dated 1993. (Box 5, Folder 306)
    - TAYLOR, MARVIN J. 3 letters; dated 1996-1998; plus catalogue of Tim Dlugos Papers at Fales Library. (Box 5, Folder 307)
    - TAYSON, RICHARD. 4 letters; ca. 1993-1997. (Box 5, Folder 308)
    - TEASLEY, LISA. 8 letters, 4 postcards, 1 card, 1 fax; dated 1995-1998; plus 2 photographs of LT in Paris with DT and Ira Silverberg. (Box 5, Folder 309)
    - TIERNEY, KARL. 2 letters, 1 postcard; dated 1992. (Box 5, Folder 310)
    - TILLMAN, LYNNE. 4 letters, 12 postcards; dated 1983-1995; plus 30 pages of prose. (Box 5, Folder 311)
    - TIMMONS, SUSIE. 1 letter; dated 1998; plus 1 page of poetry. (Box 5, Folder 312)
    - TOMKIW, LYDIA. 1 letter; ca. 1989 (Box 5, Folder 313)
    - TOPP, MIKE. 3 letters, 2 postcards; dated 1990-1998; plus two chapbooks. (Box 5, Folder 314)
    - ULIN, DAVID L. 3 letters; dated 1989-1991; plus inscribed copy of Cape Cod Blues chapbook. (Box 5, Folder 315)
    - UPSHAW, REAGAN. 1 postcard; dated 1992. (Box 5, Folder 316)
    - VALLANCE, JEFFREY. 1 postcard; dated 1983. (Box 5, Folder 317)
    - VAN MIDDHLAR, C. WOLFRAM SWETZ. 5 letters; dated 1994-1995. (Box 5, Folder 318)
    - VENTURA, FRANK. 5 emails; dated 1998. (Box 5, Folder 319)
    - VICE, LISA. 1 letter; dated 1991. (Box 5, Folder 320)
    - VIOLI, PAUL. 1 letter; dated 1998; plus 13 pages of poetry. (Box 5, Folder 321)
    - WAKOSKI, DIANE. 1 letter; dated 1998. (Box 5, Folder 322)
    - WALDMAN, ANNE. 1 postcard; dated 1991; plus 4-page questionnaire and release for Out Of This World anthology. (Box 5, Folder 323)
    - WALT, JEFF. 1 letter; dated 1992. (Box 5, Folder 324)
    - WARD, DIANE. 1 postcard; dated 1990. (Box 5, Folder 325)
    - WARSH, LEWIS. 2 letters; dated 1992. (Box 5, Folder 326)
    - WEISSMAN, BENJAMIN. 4 letters, 4 faxes; dated 1986-1997. (Box 5, Folder 327)
    - WELT, BERNARD. 5 letters; dated 1982-1997. (Box 5, Folder 328)
    - WHEELER, SUSAN. 7 letters, 52 postcards, 49 emails; dated 1990-1998; plus numerous cards, thank you notes, faxes, etc.; and draft of Acie (novel). (Box 5, Folder 329)
    - WHEELER, SUSAN. cont'd, undated (Box 5, Folder 330)
    - WHEELER, SUSAN. cont'd, undated (Box 5, Folder 331)
    - WHEELER, SUSAN. cont'd, undated (Box 5, Folder 332)
    - WHITE, AMY. 10 letters, 1 postcard, 1 email; dated 1984-1998. (Box 5, Folder 333)
    - WIEGERS, MICHAEL L. 1 letter; dated 1991. (Box 5, Folder 334)
    - WILLIAMS, MEGAN. 1 postcard; dated 1993. (Box 5, Folder 335)
    - WILSON, ERIC. 1 letter; dated 1988. (Box 5, Folder 336)
    - WINCH, TERENCE. 3 letters; dated 1991-1993. (Box 5, Folder 337)
    - WISS, CHRISTOPHER. 7 letters, 5 postcards, 1 card, 3 faxes; dated 1991-1997; plus 5 photographs of Tim Dlugos. (Box 5, Folder 338)
    - WOJAHN, DAVID. 1 letter; dated 1991. (Box 5, Folder 339)
    - YABLONSKY, LINDA. 1 card, 5 emails; dated 1997-1998. (Box 5, Folder 340)
    - YANG, NAOMI. 11 letters, 7 postcards, 1 email; dated 1993-1998. (Box 5, Folder 341)
    - ZALOPANY, MICHELE. 1 letter; dated 1991; plus 2 inscribed exhibition catalogues. (Box 5, Folder 342)
    - ZOLYNAS, AL. 4 letters; dated 1990-1992; plus permission form for Men of Our Time. (Box 5, Folder 343)
    - ZUCKER, RACHEL. 4 letters, 1 postcard, 11 emails; dated 1993-1998; plus 5 pages of poetry; and Xeroxed manuscript of "A Man of Means." (Box 5, Folder 344)
  - Subseries B: Correspondence from Family
    - TRINIDAD, JOYCE AND RUPERT (parents)., undated (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - TRINIDAD, JOYCE AND RUPERT (parents). Parents' love letters., undated (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - TRINIDAD, ROSS (brother)., undated (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - TRINIDAD, LINDA (sister; married name: Jackson)., undated (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - TRINIDAD, JENNIFER (sister)., undated (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - TRINIDAD, ANYTA (grandmother) & TRINIDAD, RUPERT (grandfather)., undated (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - RELATIVES., undated (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Subseries C: Correspondence Regarding Publications
    Scope and Contents note
    (Correspondence, fliers, permission forms, etc.)
    - MAGAZINES., undated (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - ANTHOLOGIES., undated (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Subseries D: Miscellaneous Correspondence
    - A.A. FRIENDS., undated (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - STUDENTS., undated (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - MISCELLANEOUS., undated (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Series II: Writing
  - Subseries A: Manuscripts
    - PAVANE. Definitive version, 1998. (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - PAVANE. Revised version, summer 1995. (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - PAVANE. Revised version, 1988. (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - HAND OVER HEART. Manuscript, 1990. (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - HAND OVER HEART. Correspondence from publisher, contract, correspondence from agent, corrections, cover designs, rejection letters, etc., undated (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - ANSWER SONG. Manuscript, 1992. (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - ANSWER SONG. Contract, cover designs, galleys, ads, etc., undated (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Subseries B[1]: Poetry Worksheets 4/29/75-11/30/80
    - WITH A PHONE IN HER HAND. Circa 1971. (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - IN A SUBURB OF THEBES. 4/29/75., 1975 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - THEBES. 5/5/75., 1975 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - DELPHI. 5/10/75., 1975 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - THE SPHINX. 5/11/75., 1975 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - WEDDING NIGHT. 5/12/75., 1975 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - IN PRAISE OF HIM. 6/13/75., 1975 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - FAIRY TALE. 2/4/77., 1977 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - PHANTOM. 2/17/77., 1977 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - WE DREAM OF SNAKES. 2/22/77., 1977 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - DREAM CREATURES. 2/25/77., 1977 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - CLUE. 3/8/77., 1977 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - THE PEASANT GIRL. 3/22/77., 1977 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - WARM WINTER. 5/4/77., 1977 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - HECATE. 5/5/77., 1977 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - IRIS. 5/8/77., 1977 (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - RAPUNZEL. 10/4/77., 1977 (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - THE BOY. 4/10/78., 1978 (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - NIGHT AND FOG. Easter Vacation, 1978. (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - THE GIFT OF DIONYSUS. 4/28/78., 1978 (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - THE PARTY. 9/8/78., 1978 (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - SCHOLAR. 9/30/78., 1978 (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - FALSE APOCALYPSE. 10/10/78., 1978 (Box 6, Folder 23)
    - FOR THE MAGICIAN. 11/25/78., 1978 (Box 6, Folder 24)
    - NIGHTSHADE. 6/2/79., 1979 (Box 6, Folder 25)
    - THE SORCERESS. 10/16/79., 1979 (Box 6, Folder 26)
    - NIGHTFALL. 9/4/80., 1980 (Box 6, Folder 27)
    - PAVANE. 11/30/80., 1980 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Subseries B[2]: Poetry Worksheets 5/5/81-5/4/88
    - ORDINARY THINGS. 5/5/81., 1981 (Box 6, Folder 29)
    - BEFORE MORNING. 8/31/81., 1981 (Box 6, Folder 30)
    - GREAT-GRANDMOTHER SMITH. 3/25/82., 1982 (Box 6, Folder 31)
    - TIM'S STOLEN SWEATER. 8/17/82., 1982 (Box 6, Folder 32)
    - C'EST PLUS QU'UN CRIME, C'EST UNE FAUTE. 9/21/82., 1982 (Box 6, Folder 33)
    - POEM ("again like never I feel"). 11/6/82., 1982 (Box 6, Folder 34)
    - POEM ("Sometimes it seems the night conspires"). 1/22/83., 1983 (Box 6, Folder 35)
    - SONG ("This single by the all-girl group"). 4/16/83., 1983 (Box 6, Folder 36)
    - POEM ("That vast dance floor.. ."). 5/22/83., 1983 (Box 6, Folder 37)
    - UP & DOWN. 10/11/83., 1983 (Box 6, Folder 38)
    - WINDOW SEAT. 10/21/83., 1983 (Box 6, Folder 39)
    - MY TERM PAPER ON MARILYN MONROE. 11/1/83., 1983 (Box 6, Folder 40)
    - POEM FOR BRIAN. 1/30/84., 1984 (Box 6, Folder 41)
    - I LOST MY GOLD RING TODAY. 2/16/84., 1984 (Box 6, Folder 42)
    - NEEDLEPOINT. 3/5/84., 1984 (Box 6, Folder 43)
    - MONDAY, MONDAY. 3/29/84., 1984 (Box 6, Folder 44)
    - YOUR BRAIN AT WORK. 4/11/84., 1984 (Box 6, Folder 45)
    - MICHAEL'S DREAM. 5/3/84., 1984 (Box 6, Folder 46)
    - APRIL INVENTORY. 5/9/84., 1984 (Box 6, Folder 47)
    - TO SIR WITH LOVE. 5/26/84., 1984 (Box 6, Folder 48)
    - DREAMS. 5/27/84; 8/18/85., 1984-1985 (Box 6, Folder 49)
    - MEET THE SUPREMES. 8/23/84., 1984 (Box 6, Folder 50)
    - FOOTNOTE. 9/13/84., 1984 (Box 6, Folder 51)
    - REGISTERED NURSE. 9/15/84., 1984 (Box 6, Folder 52)
    - SONNET. 9/24/84., 1984 (Box 6, Folder 53)
    - GOOD TIDINGS. 10/23/84., 1984 (Box 6, Folder 54)
    - NOSFERATU. 12/6/84., 1984 (Box 7, Folder 55)
    - IS YOUR SECRET DATE BEHIND THIS DOOR? 12/16/84., 1984 (Box 7, Folder 56)
    - ONE FINE DAY. 2/3/85., 1985 (Box 7, Folder 57)
    - LIVING DOLL. 3/4/85., 1985 (Box 7, Folder 58)
    - NOVEMBER. 12/21/85., 1985 (Box 7, Folder 59)
    - FOUR POEMS. 3/27/86., 1986 (Box 7, Folder 60)
    - FLOWER POWER. 5/14/86., 1986 (Box 7, Folder 61)
    - BEATLE FUN KIT. 5/23/86., 1986 (Box 7, Folder 62)
    - 60'S FASHION HAIKU. 6/5/86., 1986 (Box 7, Folder 63)
    - MM PAPER DOLL. 6/9/86., 1986 (Box 7, Folder 64)
    - A MILLION TO ONE. 8/3/86., 1986 (Box 7, Folder 65)
    - 10/31/84. 8/22/86., 1984-1986 (Box 7, Folder 66)
    - FOR ROY. 10/11/86., 1986 (Box 7, Folder 67)
    - FIVE HAIKU. 11/21/86., 1986 (Box 7, Folder 68)
    - MOVIN' WITH NANCY. 11/30/86., 1986 (Box 7, Folder 69)
    - POEM ("The birds"). 12/2/86., 1986 (Box 7, Folder 70)
    - LITTLE NOTHINGS. 12/15/86., 1986 (Box 7, Folder 71)
    - HAND OVER HEART. 12/18/86., 1986 (Box 7, Folder 72)
    - POEM ("To be joyous without"). 1/21/87., 1987 (Box 7, Folder 73)
    - DOUBLE TROUBLE. 3/1/87., 1987 (Box 7, Folder 74)
    - ALCOHOLIC. 3/6/87., 1987 (Box 7, Folder 75)
    - YELLOW ROOM. 4/12/87., 1987 (Box 7, Folder 76)
    - RERUNS. 4/22/87., 1987 (Box 7, Folder 77)
    - THREE FROM THE SIXTIES. 5/20/87., 1987 (Box 7, Folder 78)
    - WHAT CYNDI WEARS. 10/87., 1987 (Box 7, Folder 79)
    - FICTION WITHOUT FOOTNOTES. 10/30/87., 1987 (Box 7, Folder 80)
    - DAVID TRINIDAD. 11/18/87., 1987 (Box 7, Folder 81)
    - SECRET AGENT GIRL. 1/13/88., 1988 (Box 7, Folder 82)
    - THE GIRL IN THE CENTERFOLD. 2/18/88., 1988 (Box 7, Folder 83)
    - 3/10/88. 3/11/88., 1988 (Box 7, Folder 84)
    - 3/12/88. 3/12/88., 1988 (Box 7, Folder 85)
    - OSCAR NIGHT. 4/18/88., 1988 (Box 7, Folder 86)
    - LETTER POEM. 4/26/88., 1988 (Box 7, Folder 87)
    - THE MUNSTERS. 4/29/88., 1988 (Box 7, Folder 88)
    - GENIUS. 5/4/88., 1988 (Box 7, Folder 89)
  - Subseries B[3]: Poetry Worksheets 8/10/88-4/7/92
    - DRIVING BACK FROM NEW HAVEN. 8/10/88., 1988 (Box 7, Folder 90)
    - POME. 9/18/88., 1988 (Box 7, Folder 91)
    - PLEASANT STREET. 9/20/88., 1988 (Box 7, Folder 92)
    - 4:11 A.M. 10/1/88., 1988 (Box 7, Folder 93)
    - FIVE DREAMS. 10/4/88., 1988 (Box 7, Folder 94)
    - LOCUS SOLUS. 10/15/88., 1988 (Box 7, Folder 95)
    - WELL I WONDER. 10/17/88., 1988 (Box 7, Folder 96)
    - HOW SOON IS NOW? 10/19/88 (Box 7, Folder 97)
    - OCTOBER 22, 1988. 10/23/88. (Box 7, Folder 98)
    - SUBWAY. 10/24/88., 1988 (Box 7, Folder 99)
    - FLEUR-DE-LIS. 10/24/88., 1988 (Box 7, Folder 100)
    - JADE EAST. 10/24/88., 1988 (Box 7, Folder 101)
    - PLANET X. 10/25/88., 1988 (Box 7, Folder 102)
    - ALICE'S DREAM ASSIGNMENT. 11/3/88., 1988 (Box 7, Folder 103)
    - POEM ("Friday evening:"). 11/6/88., 1988 (Box 7, Folder 104)
    - THE PORTRAIT OF A LADY. 11/10/88., 1988 (Box 7, Folder 105)
    - BELOVED. 11/12/88., 1988 (Box 7, Folder 106)
    - NOVEMBER 23, 1988. 11/26/88. (Box 7, Folder 107)
    - WHAT DEBBIE & CAMERON LOST IN NEW YORK. 12/8/88., 1988 (Box 7, Folder 108)
    - VIOLIN. 12/19/88. (Box 7, Folder 109)
    - EARLY DAYS. 12/19/88. (Box 7, Folder 110)
    - HOCKNEY: BLUE POOL. 1/12/89., 1989 (Box 7, Folder 111)
    - HOUSESITTING AT JOAN'S. 1/15/89., 1989 (Box 7, Folder 112)
    - THE WORLD. 2/4/89., 1989 (Box 7, Folder 113)
    - SONG ('"You Don't Own Me"'). 2/22/89., 1989 (Box 7, Folder 114)
    - LINES. 3/5/89., 1989 (Box 7, Folder 115)
    - AT AN OPENING. 3/6/89., 1989 (Box 7, Folder 116)
    - AT THE END OF THE DREAM I CAN FLY. 3/7/89., 1989 (Box 7, Folder 117)
    - DELIRIOUS AFTERNOON. 3/13/89., 1989 (Box 7, Folder 118)
    - MY LOVER. 3/18.89., 1989 (Box 7, Folder 119)
    - THINGS TO DO IN VALLEY OF THE DOLLS (THE MOVIE). 4/12/89., 1989 (Box 7, Folder 120)
    - BARBARELLA. 5/14/89., 1989 (Box 7, Folder 121)
    - MOONSTONES. 5/16/89., 1989 (Box 7, Folder 122)
    - EIGHTEEN TO TWENTY-ONE. 9/3/89., 1989 (Box 7, Folder 123)
    - THE KISS. 9/22/89., 1989 (Box 7, Folder 124)
    - EVERYDAY IS LIKE SUNDAY. 9/26/89., 1989 (Box 7, Folder 125)
    - YVETTE MIMIEUX IN HIT LADY. 10/1/89., 1989 (Box 7, Folder 126)
    - LOVE POEM. 10/15/89., 1989 (Box 7, Folder 127)
    - LAST NIGHT. 11/7/89., 1989 (Box 7, Folder 128)
    - A PHOTOGRAPH. 11/29/89., 1989 (Box 7, Folder 129)
    - SUNDAY EVENING. 12/4/89., 1989 (Box 7, Folder 130)
    - WEDNESDAY MORNING. 1/7/90., 1990 (Box 7, Folder 131)
    - DEAD FLOWERS. 1/23/90., 1990 (Box 7, Folder 132)
    - THE WANDERER. January 30, 1990. (Box 7, Folder 133)
    - POLAROID COLLAGE: GREGORY. February 3, 1990. (Box 7, Folder 134)
    - TRANSLATION. 3/8/90., 1990 (Box 7, Folder 135)
    - PEE SHY. 3/14/90., 1990 (Box 7, Folder 136)
    - ANSWER SONG. 4/3/90., 1990 (Box 7, Folder 137)
    - PLAYING WITH DOLLS. 4/11/90., 1990 (Box 7, Folder 138)
    - IT'S NOT UNUSUAL. 5/7/90., 1990 (Box 7, Folder 139)
    - GHOSTS. 7/20/90., 1990 (Box 7, Folder 140)
    - THE BOMB SHELTER. 8/19/90. (Box 7, Folder 141)
    - TEENAGERS FROM OUTER SPACE. 8/28/90., 1990 (Box 7, Folder 142)
    - FANTASIA ON ACID. 9/6/90., 1990 (Box 7, Folder 143)
    - 3 A.M. 9/14/90., 1990 (Box 7, Folder 144)
    - POEM ("I drank too much coffee"). 11/8/90., 1990 (Box 7, Folder 145)
    - UNTITLED. 1/18/91., 1991 (Box 7, Folder 146)
    - IT'S A WIG! 4/22/91., 1991 (Box 7, Folder 147)
    - IT. 5/7/91., 1991 (Box 7, Folder 148)
    - INNER BOOM. 6/3/91., 1991 (Box 7, Folder 149)
    - (DOLL NOT INCLUDED). 8/3/91., 1991 (Box 7, Folder 150)
    - WHAT IRA SAID IN HIS SLEEP. 8/6/91., 1991 (Box 7, Folder 151)
    - THE TEN BEST EPISODES OF THE PATTY DUKE SHOW. 8/10/91., 1991 (Box 7, Folder 152)
    - POSTCARD FROM CHERRY GROVE. 9/7/91., 1991 (Box 7, Folder 153)
    - THE SHOWER SCENE IN PSYCHO. 10/3/91., 1991 (Box 7, Folder 154)
    - INVASION. 10/5/91., 1991 (Box 7, Folder 155)
    - FAMILY PORTRAIT, 1963. 10/29/91., 1991 (Box 7, Folder 156)
    - THREE DEATHS. 1/29/92., 1992 (Box 7, Folder 157)
    - CINNAMON TOAST. 3/28/92., 1992 (Box 7, Folder 158)
    - AT THE GLASS ONION, 1971. 4/2/92., 1992 (Box 7, Folder 159)
    - PACOIMA, CALIFORNIA, 1956. 4/7/92., 1992 (Box 7, Folder 160)
  - Subseries B[4]: Poetry Worksheets 5/17/92-7/25/97
    - BROKEN TOY. 5/17/92., 1992 (Box 7, Folder 161)
    - LOVE SCENE FROM VALLEY OF THE DOLLS AS A "LANGUAGE" POEM. 7/10/92., 1992 (Box 7, Folder 162)
    - DETECTIVE NOTES. 7/92., 1992 (Box 7, Folder 163)
    - BEWITCHED. 9/8/92., 1992 (Box 7, Folder 164)
    - SOMETHING'S GOT TO GIVE. 10/12/92., 1992 (Box 7, Folder 165)
    - ANCIENT HISTORY. 1/22/93., 1993 (Box 7, Folder 166)
    - ACCESSORIES. 2/13/93., 1993 (Box 7, Folder 167)
    - CLAIM TO FAME. 2/93., 1993 (Box 7, Folder 168)
    - FLUFF. 3/5/94., 1994 (Box 7, Folder 169)
    - ESSAY WITH MOVABLE PARTS. 8/4/94., 1994 (Box 7, Folder 170)
    - ESSAY WITH MOVABLE PARTS. 8/4/94. (cont'd), 1994 (Box 7, Folder 171)
    - BITS 'N PIECES. 12/11/94., 1994 (Box 7, Folder 172)
    - THE GAME OF LIFE. 12/27/94., 1994 (Box 7, Folder 173)
    - MONSTER MASH. 2/19/95. (Box 7, Folder 174)
    - RED PARADE. 2/25/95., 1995 (Box 7, Folder 175)
    - DIRECTIONS. 4/30/95., 1995 (Box 7, Folder 176)
    - PLASTICVILLE. 6/7/95., 1995 (Box 7, Folder 177)
    - OF MERE PLASTIC. 6/20/95., 1995 (Box 7, Folder 178)
    - CHATTY CATHY VILLANELLE. 7/30/95., 1995 (Box 7, Folder 179)
    - PINK POEMS. 10/8/95., 1995 (Box 7, Folder 180)
    - ARABESQUE, GAMBIT, CAPRICE, CHARADE, AND MIRAGE. 1/10/96., 1996 (Box 7, Folder 181)
    - DAVID'S POST-ITS. 4/2/96., 1996 (Box 7, Folder 182)
    - FORTUNES. 7/1/96., 1996 (Box 7, Folder 183)
    - CLUE (Revised). 10/96., 1996 (Box 7, Folder 184)
    - EVERY NIGHT, BYRON! 1/24/97., 1997 (Box 7, Folder 185)
    - EVENING TWILIGHT. 3/5/97., 1997 (Box 7, Folder 186)
    - FAT LIZ/BAD ANNE. 3/7/97., 1997 (Box 7, Folder 187)
    - THE LOVE MACHINE. 5/16/97., 1997 (Box 7, Folder 188)
    - IN MY ROOM. 6/27/97., 1997 (Box 7, Folder 189)
    - GARBO'S TROLLS. 7/25/97., 1997 (Box 7, Folder 190)
  - Subseries C: Collaborations 1981-1992
    [in one folder]
    - THE ORDEAL. With Dennis Cooper. 12/14/81., 1981 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - THREE POEMS. With Kim Rosenfield & Jack Skelley. 4/82., 1982 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - COLUMBUS DAY. With Tim Dlugos. 10/11/82., 1982 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - MUSSO & FRANK. With Amy Gerstler, Eileen Myles & Jack Skelley. 12/14/82., 1982 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - RAINBOW PENCIL. With Amy Gerstler. 1/13/83., 1983 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - FROLIC. With Monica Rex, Jack Skelley, etc. 7/3/83., 1983 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - WAITING FOR COCAINE. With Amy Gerstler. 9/9/83., 1983 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - S.O.S. With Dennis Cooper. 1/19/85. (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - CLOUD. With Amy Gerstler. 6/13/86., 1986 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - SAINT. With Amy Gerstler. 12/14/86., 1986 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - A TASTE OF HONEY (12 poems). With Bob Flanagan. 7/86-7/87., 1987 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - BOSSA NOVA BABY. With Elaine Equi & Jerome Sala. 8/6/88., 1988 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - TEQUILA SUNRISE. With Elaine Equi & Jerome Sala. Christmas, 1988. (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - LOSING THORN. With Janet Gray. 7/8/89., 1989 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - 13 GHOSTS. With Bob Flanagan. 9/16/90-5/19/92., 1990-1992 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Subseries D: Book Reviews 1990-1996
    - Stations, Assotto Saint. The James White Review; winter 1990. (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Ballerina Criminology, Connie Deanovich. The Poetry Project Newsletter; Feb./March 1991. (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - AIDS in America, Long Shot magazine. OutWeek; March 20, 1991. (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Bethlehem in Broad Daylight, Mark Doty. OutWeek; June 19, 1991. (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Ceremonies, Essex Hemphill. Voice Literary Supplement; June 1992. [see also Oversize, Ser. IV N, F. 1] (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Tasker Street, Mark Halliday. Voice Literary Supplement; November 1992. [see also Oversize, Ser. IV N, F. 2] (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Miss Pamela's Mercy, Lynn Crosbie. Voice Literary Supplement; March 1993. [see also Oversize, Ser. IV N, F. 3] (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Line Breaks (Bent Antenna, Curt Anderson; The Red Line, Betsy Sholl; Vox Angelica, Timothy Liu; Smile!, Denise Duhamel). Los Angeles Reader; April 1993. [see also Oversize, Ser. IV N, F. 4] (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Line Breaks (Wife, Jim Cory; Ted, Ron Padgett; My Tokyo, Frederick Seidel). Los Angeles Reader; July 1993. [see also Oversize, Ser. IV N, F. 4] (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - City Poet: The Life and Times of Frank O'Hara, Brad Gooch. Out; July 1993. (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Line Breaks (The Descent of Alette, Alice Notley). Los Angeles Reader; October 1993. [see also Oversize, Ser. IV N, F. 4] (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Whores of Lost Atlantis, Charles Busch. Killed by Details; October 1993. (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Line Breaks (Joan Jobe Smith, Jehovah Jukebox). Los Angeles Reader; December 1993. [see also Oversize, Ser. IV N, F. 4] (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Barbie in Fashion. Out; July/August 1994. (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Forever Barbie: The Unauthorized Biography of a Real Doll, M.G. Lord. New York. Newsday; November 20, 1994. [see also Oversize, Ser. IV N, F. 5] (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Our Paris: Sketches from Memory, Edmund White. New York Newsday; November 19, 1995. [see also Oversize, Ser. IV N, F. 6] (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - Selected Poems 1947-1995, Allen Ginsberg. Out; October 1996. (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Subseries E: Interviews
    - Dennis Cooper: Of Idols and Innocence. Bachy 18; 1981. (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Adrienne Rich Charts a Difficult World. The Advocate; December 31, 1991. (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Dream of Life: Patti Smith Gets Carried Away. Los Angeles Reader; April 29, 1994. [see also Oversize, Ser. IV N, F. 7] (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Subseries F: Essays
    - In the Midnight Hour: Helter Skelter Turns Twenty-Five. Los Angeles Reader; October, 1994. [see also Oversize, Ser. IV N, F. 8] (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - The Big Valley (On Valley of the Dolls and Jacqueline Susann). 1997 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Subseries G: Miscellaneous Writing
    - On "Reruns." The Best American Poetry 1991; 1991. (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Introduction to Tim Dlugos's Strong Place. Amethyst Press; 1992. (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Introduction to 5 x 7. 1993 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - On "Monday, Monday" and "Meet The Supremes." Sweet Nothings; 1994. (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Influences: Anne Sexton. Voice Literary Supplement; April 1994. [see also Oversize, Ser. IV N, F. 9] (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Editor's Note to Powerless by Tim Dlugos. High Risk Books; 1996. (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - The Worst Reading I Ever Gave (for KGB anthology). 1998 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Accretion 2006.106 (Box 16, Folder 1-3)
  - Subseries H
    (in one folder)
    - Blurbs, undated (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - 1992: Cape Cod Blues, David L., undated (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - 1993: Tim and Pete, James Robert Baker., undated (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - 1993: A Hundred Flowers, Janet Gray., undated (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - 1993: Skulls Head Samba, Eve Packer., undated (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - 1993: What is Found There, Adrienne Rich., undated (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - 1994: City of God, Gil Cuadros., undated (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - 1994: Crazy Love Rides, Holly Scalera., undated (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - 1995: Blood Poisoning, Jeffery Conway., undated (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - 1996: Girl Soldier, Denise Duhamel., undated (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - 1998: Queen Rat, Lynn Crosbie., undated (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Series III: Publications
  - Subseries A: Books
    All items have been removed to the Downtown Collection, and cataloged- see "Separated Materials" for a complete listing
  - Subseries B: Anthologies 1980-1997.
    Many items have been separared from the collection, and are accessible through BobCat. See "Separated Materials" for a listing.
    - COMING ATTRACTIONS: AN ANTHOLOGY OF AMERICAN POETS IN THEIR TWENTIES. Edited by Dennis Cooper; Little Caesar Press; 1980. Poems: "Phantom," "The Sorceress," "Rapunzel," "The Party." (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Subseries C: Magazines 1976-1998
    Many of the items in this subseries have been separated from the collection, and integrated into the Downtown Materials. See "Separated Materials" for a listing.
    - PRIZE POETS '76. 1976 Poem: "The Beachcomber" (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - THE GRAMERCY REVIEW. Vol. 1, No. 3; July 1977. Poem: "Iris." (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - THE GRAMERCY REVIEW. Vol. 2, No. 2; spring 1978. Poem: "Dream Creatures.", 1978-1979 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - ANGEL'S FLIGHT. 1979 Poem: "Scholar" (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - THE GRAMERCY REVIEW. Vol. 3, No. 4; autumn 1979. Poem: "For the Magician." (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - BACHY. No. 16; winter 1980. Poems: "Delphi," "Thebes," "Wedding Night," "The Sphinx," "The Boy," "In Praise of Him" (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - ANGEL'S FLIGHT. Vol. 5, No. 1; spring 1980. Poems: "Fairy Tale," "The Red Ledge," "False Apocalypse." (Box 8, Folder 7)